const STORE = [
  //00
  {
    question: "What is A?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "A"
  },
  //01  
  {
    question: "What is B?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "B"
  },
  //02
  {
    question: "What is C?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "C"
  },
   //03
  {
    question: "What is D?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "D"
  },
   //04
  {
    question: "What is C?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "C"
  },
   //05
  {
    question: "What is B?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "B"
  },
   //06
  {
    question: "What is A?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "A"
  },
   //07
  {
    question: "What is B?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "B"
  },
   //08
  {
    question: "What is C?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "C"
  },
   //09
  {
    question: "What is D?",
    choices: ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
    answer: "D"
  },
]

let correctAnswers = 0;
let currentQuestion = 0;


